

Contact

Address: Travessa Dom Amando, nº 984, NBH Santa Clara, Santarém -

PA, Brazil E-mail:

joaopauloalencarrodriguesagmail.com

Github: github.com/joaorodrs

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/joaorodrs

Certifications

IGNITE REACT

Rocketseat Education - 2023

IGNITE REACT NATIVE

Rocketseat Education - 2022

Languages

- English (Advanced)
- Portuguese (Native)

João Rodrigues

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Personal Summary

Software Developer with 2 years of experience working with complex web and mobile solutions for various companies and clients. I am currently looking for a job as a Junior Developer.

Core Skills

- Proficiency in ReactJS development.
- Basic VueJS knowledge
- Software testing knowledge.
- Strong problem solving skills.
- Excellence in verbal and written communication

Work Experience

DEV. JUNIOR WEB / MOBILE

Inovan.do / March 2021 - present

- Dashboard admin pages creation and maintenance
- Solutions using geolocalization API's and maps for specific projects
- Budget meetings

DEV. FULLSTACK

Eu Fit Brasil (freelance) / April 2020 - January 2021

- React Native mobile app for Android and IOS
- NodeJS API serving the app
- App deployment in AppStore and Google Play Store, and API deploy into Digital Ocean

Education

UNAMA -AMAZON UNIVERSITY

BSc. Business | March 2021 - present Studying business adminstration

- Leadership and team management
- Organization, systems and methods
- Business law

INSTITUTO FEDERAL DO PARÁ

High School | January 2018 - December 2020